So this story needs everyone's attention.
So there are around 50 US citizens who have been exposed to Ebola in the DRC
who are going to be quarantined in Kenya,
even though there's no single recorded case in Kenya.
Now, the Kenyan High Court ruled that this was unconstitutional two days ago.
But despite that, the sellout William Ruto administration has decided to go ahead with it anyway.
The Kenyan people are not having it and they were protesting today
and they were met with the brutality that we're used to seeing here in Kenya.
Rubber bullets, tear gas taken to police cells, most likely beaten up and tortured
for protesting in accordance with the Kenyan High Court ruling.
Now, this is happening in La Kipia County, which is already the site of Batouk,
the largest British overseas military base,
which is the largest military base that Britain has anywhere in the world,
five times bigger than the military base in Salisbury,
bigger than any military base that they have in any overseas territory,
is here in Kenya, where British soldiers have been accused of murder,
rape, abuse, fathering Kenyan children and abandoning them.
And according to an Amnesty International report,
there's been over 650 alleged rape cases against women and children
by British soldiers in La Kipia County that have gone unpunished.
This is already a colonized space and now the Americans are getting in on the act.
So yeah, we need more support to push back against this.
We need Americans in the US to talk about this.
I've not seen anyone US side talking about this.
We need your support because this is colonialism one-on-one
and it's happening here in Kenya in 2026.
Thanks.